<Tutorials>
		<Title>Tutorials</Title>
		<Help>Access to the Tutorials of the Wind Farm Simulator suite and special applications</Help>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe -n C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\Help\English\LdP_Help\Introduction.html</Exec>
			<Title>LdP Simulators platform</Title>
			<Help>LdP is the platform where the Simulators are executed.
			<p>This tutorial describes all the functionalities that are common to every one of the Simulators in the WindFarmSimulator suite, including the description of the following synoptics: 
			<ul>
			<li>Parameters</li>
			<li>Connections editor</li>
			<li>Strip recorders</li></ul> 
			<p>It also includes their functionalities as <b>Virtual Work Bench</b>, the structure of the <b>data bases</b> that record the evolution of the signals in the simulator, and how to export them in worksheet format.</p>
			</p>
			</Help>
		</Tutorial>	
		
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe -n  C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\Help\English\Wind_Farm_Simulator_SCADA\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>Wind Farm SCADA Simulator</Title>
			<Help>With this Simulator you can learn the concepts involved in the Operation of a Wind Farm, the datalogging and control of the Wind Turbines, the Meteorological Station, the electric Substation, the connections between the, as well as aspects related to the Production Planning as function of Wind Forecast, the Maintenance Planning, and custormer relationships.
			</Help>
		</Tutorial>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe -n C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\Help\English\DSASWTSimulator\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>Active Stall Wind Turbine Simulator</Title>
			<Help>With this Simulator you can explore the components and subsystems of a industrial grade Wind Turbine.
			<p>This version corresponds to a Wind Turbine with a squirrel cage (shortcuited rotor winding) electric generator, directly connected to the Grid.</p>
			<p>The control of the Drive Train is done using the method known as 'Active Stall': controlled <i>stalling</i> using the blades Pitch.</p>
			</Help>
		</Tutorial>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe -n C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\Help\English\RRCWTSimulator\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>Rotor Resistance Controlled  Wind Turbine Simulator</Title>
			<Help>Rotor Resistance Controlled Wind Turbines were a key step in the evolution of the Wind Turbine technologies for controlling the Drive Train, specially for coping with the problems related to wind gusts response.
			<p>With this simulator you can observe the important aspects of this approach, and be ready to understand the behavior of the modern Wind Turbine technologies (DFIG).</p>
			</Help>
		</Tutorial>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe -n C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\Help\English\DFIGWTSimulator\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>DFIG Wind Turbine Simulator</Title>
			<Help>With this Simulator you can observe the <b>complex functionalities</b> used to control the Drive Train of Variable Speed Wind Turbines.
			<p>In this particular case, this is achieved using the capabilities of an special Power Electronics device called Back-to-Back converter, connected to the rotor winding.</p>
			<p>You will be able to observe all the changes in the electric, magnetic and mechanic variables of the electric Generator (Induction Generator).</p>
			<p>This Wind Turbine family allows for the setting of the <i>requested</i> Active and Reactive Power delivered to the Grid.</p>
			<p>The DFIG also are designed to obtain the maximum power from the wind when wind speed is below <i>nominal wind speed</i>.</p></Help>
		</Tutorial>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe  -n  C:\ACMSL\OperationalCurveVarSpeedWTs\Help\English\OperationalCurveVarSpeedWTsr12\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>Operational Curve of Variable Speed Wind Turbines</Title>
			<Help>To achieve maximum transfer of energy from te existing wind the Drive Train must be controlled according to specific rules that depends on the actual wind speed, the Drive Train rotational speed, the characteristics of the blades, and several other factors.
			<p>This application computes, and presents graphically, the key variables of the Wind Turbine : 
			<ul>
			<li>Power versus RPMs</li>
			<li>Power versus Wind Speed</li>
			<li>RPMs versus Wind Speed</li>
			<li>Blades Pitch versus Wind Spped</li>
			</ul>  
			</p>
			<p>It can be used for computing the influence of the Operation Curve control parameters on the Power versus Wind Speed.</p>
			<p>Or the influence of longer blades on gearbox ratio and delivered power in repowering projects.</p>
			</Help>
		</Tutorial>
		<Tutorial>
			<Exec>C:\ACMSL\WindFarmSimulator\ViewerTutorialsWFSr12.exe  -n C:\ACMSL\DFIGB2B\Help\English\DFIGB2Br12\Introduction.htmle</Exec>
			<Title>Computations for the Induction Generator variables and demand on the Back-to-Back Converter used in DFIGs</Title>
			<Help>The Induction Generator with Wound Rotor in DFIGs Wind Turbines are used in very special operational conditions, notably very much off their synchronous speed.
			<p>This is achieve controlling the signals that go in and out of the Rotor Winding, including its frequency, voltage, current and their phases relative to the Stator winding variables. These variables are received/forced by the Back-to-Back Converter, what makes this device a sophisticated piece.</p>
			<p>This application has been developped to ascertain the working conditions of this Back-to-Back Converter under all mechanical and electrical demands that may occur in a working DFIG Wind Turbine, in normal and exceptional situations, so that it can be dimensioned properly.</p>
			<p>You may change:
			<ul>
			<li>The <i>RPMs</i> of the Generator rotor.</li>
			<li>The <i>mechanical power</i> applied to the Generator rotor: either as Torque or Power.</li>
			<li>The set points for the <i>demanded power</i> delivered to the Grid, both Active and Reactive Power</li>
			</ul></p></Help>
		</Tutorial>
	</Tutorials>